[{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980217725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":19916,"timeElapsed":78003},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980225194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7468,"timeElapsed":85472},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980229434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4239,"timeElapsed":89712},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980232573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3138,"timeElapsed":92851},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980239895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":7321,"timeElapsed":100173},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980248418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":8522,"timeElapsed":108696},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980256066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7647,"timeElapsed":116344},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980264990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":8923,"timeElapsed":125268},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980272034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7043,"timeElapsed":132312},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980281729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7929,"timeElapsed":142007},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980284805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3075,"timeElapsed":145083},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980290783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5977,"timeElapsed":151061},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980293798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3014,"timeElapsed":154076},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980296212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2413,"timeElapsed":156490},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980300034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3821,"timeElapsed":160311},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980302614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2579,"timeElapsed":162891},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980307035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4420,"timeElapsed":167313},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980310228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3192,"timeElapsed":170506},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980326921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":14593,"timeElapsed":187199},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980329134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2213,"timeElapsed":189412},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980332921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3786,"timeElapsed":193199},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980335963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3041,"timeElapsed":196241},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980339958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3994,"timeElapsed":200236},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980344140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4181,"timeElapsed":204418},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980347326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3185,"timeElapsed":207604},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980352443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5116,"timeElapsed":212721},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980356151,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3707,"timeElapsed":216429},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980368363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":10631,"timeElapsed":228641},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980370565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2201,"timeElapsed":230843},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980373271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2705,"timeElapsed":233549},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980375780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2508,"timeElapsed":236058},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980383769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":7988,"timeElapsed":244047},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980387399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3629,"timeElapsed":247677},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980390846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3446,"timeElapsed":251124},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980394778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3931,"timeElapsed":255056},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980397879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3100,"timeElapsed":258157},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980418569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":14794,"timeElapsed":278847},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980420924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2354,"timeElapsed":281202},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980423217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2292,"timeElapsed":283495},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980425449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2232,"timeElapsed":285727},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980428116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2666,"timeElapsed":288394},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5092,"timeElapsed":293487},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980436484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3274,"timeElapsed":296762},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980467191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":30707,"timeElapsed":327469},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2778,"timeElapsed":330248},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980480671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":9201,"timeElapsed":340949},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2187,"timeElapsed":343138},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980485802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2942,"timeElapsed":346080},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980489717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3914,"timeElapsed":349995},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980494500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4782,"timeElapsed":354778},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6991,"timeElapsed":361770},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980503508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2015,"timeElapsed":363786},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":7507,"timeElapsed":371294},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980513403,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2386,"timeElapsed":373681},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980524053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":9087,"timeElapsed":384331},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1922,"timeElapsed":386254},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1879,"timeElapsed":388134},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980530466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2609,"timeElapsed":390744},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980534988,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4521,"timeElapsed":395266},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2807,"timeElapsed":398074},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6737,"timeElapsed":404812},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3478,"timeElapsed":408291},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6292,"timeElapsed":414584},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2638,"timeElapsed":417223},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":7729,"timeElapsed":430404},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2688,"timeElapsed":433093},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1838,"timeElapsed":434932},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578337,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3682,"timeElapsed":438615},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980582710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4372,"timeElapsed":442988},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980585823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3112,"timeElapsed":446101},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980588895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3071,"timeElapsed":449173},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4655,"timeElapsed":453828},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":30841,"timeElapsed":484670},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980627095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2702,"timeElapsed":487373},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3373,"timeElapsed":492130},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980633751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1898,"timeElapsed":494029},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980636621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2869,"timeElapsed":496899},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980639098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2476,"timeElapsed":499376},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980641936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2836,"timeElapsed":502214},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980645766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3830,"timeElapsed":506044},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980650796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5029,"timeElapsed":511074},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4469,"timeElapsed":515544},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980658996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3729,"timeElapsed":519274},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980667933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":7288,"timeElapsed":528211},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980670171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2237,"timeElapsed":530449},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3350,"timeElapsed":533800},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980675746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2223,"timeElapsed":536024},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980678179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2432,"timeElapsed":538457},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2492,"timeElapsed":540950},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980682782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2109,"timeElapsed":543060},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980694919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":12136,"timeElapsed":555197},{"subjectID":"1c9990a4uu","prolificID":"666a1e606b80f9865c1f3d5f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b227c49eab479546ebb6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980699596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4676,"timeElapsed":559874}]